Simon Fraser University Library fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- University Librarian's records, 1964 - 1995; F-50-1; 2.18 m of textual records
  - Reports and policies, 1964 - 1995; F-50-1-2; 46 cm of textual records
    - Meetings with Vice-President, Academic, 1970 - 1977; F-50-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-13)
    - Proposed Library Additions, 1971; F-50-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-13)
    - Report of the University Library Review Committee, 1991; F-50-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-13)
    - Three Universities Press proposal, 1967; F-50-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-13)
    - Lost book replacement policy, 1982; F-50-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-68)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/1a.
    - Regulations, 1969 - 1981; F-50-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-68)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/2.
    - Management planning, vol. 1, 1969 - 1986; F-50-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/10.
    - Management planning, vol. 2, 1969 - 1986; F-50-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Reports and tasks, 1978 - 1979; F-50-1-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Library review, 1982 - 1987; F-50-1-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Library review, 1991; F-50-1-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Library - 10 year projection, 1982; F-50-1-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Weeding/collections space policies, 1971 - 1988; F-50-1-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-69)
    - Library administration - cards/fines, vol. 1, 1966 - 1981; F-50-1-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/11.
    - Library administration - cards/fines, vol. 2, 1966 - 1981; F-50-1-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
    - "Why we have too few librarians" report, 1977; F-50-1-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
    - Departmental review - A.U.L. planning and budgeting, 1973; F-50-1-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
      Creator's original file classification code: 8000/6.
    - Annual reports, 1964 - 1969; F-50-1-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
    - Annual reports, 1970 - 1975; F-50-1-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/26.
    - Annual reports, 1976 - 1977; F-50-1-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/8.
    - Annual reports, 1983 - 1993; F-50-1-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-70)
    - Student and faculty surveys, 1994 - 1995; F-50-1-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-83)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3000/12a.
    - Downtown Library site project report, 1985; F-50-1-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
    - A report on microfilms at SFU Library, 1985; F-50-1-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-93)
- Administration records, 1964 - 1999; F-50-2; 1.72 m of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the daily administration of the University Library including organizational charts and identification of Library objectives; formulation of policies and procedures; management of staff and personnel issues including salaries, job descriptions, and grievances; monthly departmental statistics and reports; thesis preparation and binding; funding for staff research and bibliographic projects; implementation of fire and emergency procedures; budget planning and financial working papers; and management of the Audio Visual Centre.
  Records include correspondence and working papers, statistics, reports, budgets and newspaper clippings.
  - General, 1964 - 1999; F-50-2-1; 1.19 m of textual records
    - Organization Charts, 1966 - 1975; F-50-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Library Classification Titles, 1970 - 1975; F-50-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Objectives, 1971 - 1974; F-50-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Library Support Administrative Communication, Serial 1-69, 1970 - 1971; F-50-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Library Support Administrative Communication, Communication, Serial 70-143, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1965 - 1968; F-50-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1969; F-50-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1970; F-50-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1972; F-50-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel, 1973 - 1974; F-50-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Papers, 1972 - 1974; F-50-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Personnel/Papers, 1971 - 1972; F-50-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-14)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1968; F-50-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1969; F-50-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1970; F-50-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1971; F-50-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1972; F-50-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1972; F-50-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1972; F-50-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Monthly Statistics and Reports, 1972; F-50-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-15)
    - Statistical Studies, 1965 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Librarians Salaries, 1966 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Status of Librarians, 1966 - 1971; F-50-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Status of Librarians, 1972 - 1976; F-50-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Study Leave, 1976 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - History of Library Rules and Regulations, 1965 - 1971; F-50-2-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Library Building, 1964 - 1971; F-50-2-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Departmental Review, 1973; F-50-2-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Comments on Review, 1974; F-50-2-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Audio Visual Centre, 1967 - 1971; F-50-2-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-16)
    - Library security - Tattle Tape, 1976 - 1978; F-50-2-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - Staff job grading - generic descriptions, 1979 - 1983; F-50-2-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - Visually handicapped, 1976 - 1981; F-50-2-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/14.
    - Library reorganization, 1979 - 1980; F-50-2-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - Thesis, 1996 - 1997; F-50-2-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - Union grievances, 1986 - 1987; F-50-2-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - Online Public Access Catalogue (OPAC) users guide, 1987 - 1989; F-50-2-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 50-72)
    - President's research grant, 1966 - 1974; F-50-2-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7003/6.
    - Belzberg Librarian(s) search, 1988 - 1989; F-50-2-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/73/8.
    - Microfilm of subject catalogue, 1970 - 1985; F-50-2-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/66.
    - Recon, 1979 - 1985; F-50-2-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/22.
    - Librarian's office, 1967 - 1986; F-50-2-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/6.
    - Library reorganization, vol. 1, 1975; F-50-2-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
    - Library reorganization, vol. 2, 1975; F-50-2-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
    - Library inventory, 1968 - 1981; F-50-2-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 50-73)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4000/41.
    - Library - 10 year projection, 1992; F-50-2-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - Organizational implications of centralized reference on 3rd floor, 1984 - 1985; F-50-2-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - OJAC project, 1989 - 1993; F-50-2-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - Administrative Project Team/Work Assessment Project, 1974; F-50-2-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
      Creator's original file classification code: II-A-9.
    - Control of smoking and eating, 1976 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - Standing order examination, 1967 - 1983; F-50-2-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/21/4.
    - Library Assistant Scheme, 1974; F-50-2-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
      Creator's original file classification code: I-K-5.6.
    - Thesis preparation and binding, vol. 1, 1967 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/19.
    - Thesis preparation and binding, vol. 2, 1967 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - Negative bibliographies, 1978 - 1979; F-50-2-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 50-74)
    - OJAC project - Electronic Library Network, 1993 - 1995; F-50-2-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 50-75)
    - Library computing equipment, vol. 1, 1987 - 1991; F-50-2-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 50-75)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54.
    - Library computing equipment, vol. 2, 1987 - 1991; F-50-2-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 50-75)
    - Innovation fund, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-50-2-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 50-75)
    - Innovation fund, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-50-2-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 50-75)
    - Instructional Development grant, 1997 - 1999; F-50-2-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
    - Departmental library representatives, 1980 - 1983; F-50-2-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/5.
    - Open Learning Institute, 1979 - 1981; F-50-2-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
    - Printed matter - pamphlets, 1970 - 1972; F-50-2-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/48.
    - Censorship - Playboy, 1982; F-50-2-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/80.
    - OJAC report, 1993; F-50-2-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
    - Directional and information source library queries, 1992 - 1993; F-50-2-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/159.
    - Computer Information Retrieval Services (CIRS), 1977 - 1984; F-50-2-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/41.
    - Non-print media, 1970 - 1976; F-50-2-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/51.
    - Newspapers, 1970 - 1972; F-50-2-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 50-76)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/44.
    - Winegard, 1976; F-50-2-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
      Creator's original file classification code: 9000/26.
    - Fire and emergency procedures, 1968 - 1981; F-50-2-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
    - Library computing equipment, 1984 - 1987; F-50-2-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
    - Collection weeding, 1985 - 1988; F-50-2-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/89.
    - Government documents, 1971 - 1984; F-50-2-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/35d.
    - W.A.C. Bennett Library dedication, 1981 - 1982; F-50-2-1-0-80 (Archival box - standard 50-77)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/68.
    - Virtual Canadian Union Catalogue (VCUC) pilot project, 1996 - 1998; F-50-2-1-0-81 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
    - Media exchange cooperative (film purchase), 1972 - 1976; F-50-2-1-0-82 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/46.
    - Reference service, 1975 - 1977; F-50-2-1-0-83 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/57.
  - Policies and procedures, 1970 - 1985; F-50-2-2; 13 cm of textual records
    - Policies and Procedures, 1970 - 1977; F-50-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-17)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1982 - 1984; F-50-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-17)
    - Policy Papers, 1982 - 1985; F-50-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-17)
  - Budget, 1968 - 1999; F-50-2-3; 34 cm of textual records
    - Budget Preparation, 1968; F-50-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1969; F-50-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1970; F-50-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1971; F-50-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1972; F-50-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1973; F-50-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1974; F-50-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Preparation, 1975; F-50-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Commitment Report (Sample), 1972; F-50-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget Control Report, 1968 - 1970; F-50-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-18)
    - Budget, 1984 - 1985; F-50-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
    - Budget, 1985 - 1986; F-50-2-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
    - Budget, 1986 - 1987; F-50-2-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
      Creator's original file classification code: 500/4.
    - Budget, 1987 - 1988; F-50-2-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
    - Budget, 1988 - 1989; F-50-2-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-78)
    - Budget, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-50-2-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-79)
    - Budget, vol. 2, 1996 - 1997; F-50-2-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-79)
    - Budget - working papers, 1996 - 1997; F-50-2-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-79)
    - Budget, 1997 - 1998; F-50-2-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-79)
    - Budget, 1998 - 1999; F-50-2-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-79)
  - Support Services, 1968 - 1976; F-50-2-4; 6 cm of textual records
    - Research Assistant Correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-50-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-19)
    - Research Assistant Chronological, 1969; F-50-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-19)
    - Administrative Assistant Chronological, 1968; F-50-2-4-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-19)
    - Bibliographic Control Librarian Correspondence, 1976; F-50-2-4-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-19)
- Collections Division records, 1965 - 1992; F-50-3; 1.13 m of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the activities of the Collections Division within the University Library and includes correspondence with the university community and book vendors; collection policies and analysis; monthly reports and statistics; literature guides; progress updates on the Library's early Canadian journals project and the RCMP collection; and grant applications for project funding from the Donner Foundation, Canada Library Council, Vancouver Foundation, and Boag Foundation.
  Records include correspondence, working papers and invoices, reports, statistics, grant applications, and annual reports.
  Donner Canadian Foundation; Vancouver Foundation; Boag Foundation; Canada Library Council; Royal Canadian Mounted Police
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1965 - 1992; F-50-3-1; 50 cm of textual records
    Correspondence is arranged chronologically.
    - Correspondence, 1965; F-50-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1965; F-50-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-50-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-50-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-50-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-50-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-50-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-50-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-50-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-50-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-20)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-50-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-50-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-50-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1972; F-50-3-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1973; F-50-3-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-50-3-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Memoranda, 1969 - 1971; F-50-3-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Memoranda, 1972; F-50-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Memoranda, 1973; F-50-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Memoranda, 1974; F-50-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-21)
    - Chronological, 1970; F-50-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1970; F-50-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1971; F-50-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1971; F-50-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1972; F-50-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1972; F-50-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1973; F-50-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1974; F-50-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Chronological, 1974; F-50-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - small 50-22)
    - Collections correspondence, 1968 - 1986; F-50-3-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
    - Sale/lease of library collection, 1987 - 1988; F-50-3-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/28.
    - Collection analysis, vol. 1, 1969 - 1984; F-50-3-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/30.
    - Collection analysis, vol. 2, 1969 - 1984; F-50-3-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
    - Collection analysis, vol. 3, 1969 - 1984; F-50-3-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
    - Science collection, 1973 - 1988; F-50-3-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/32.
    - Collections policies, 1974 - 1982; F-50-3-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
    - RDL, vol. 1, 1982 - 1986; F-50-3-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 50-80)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/32/1.
    - RDL, vol. 2, 1982 - 1986; F-50-3-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
    - Collections correspondence, vol. 1, 1979 - 1992; F-50-3-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
    - Collections correspondence, vol. 2, 1979 - 1992; F-50-3-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 50-87)
  - Social Sciences and Humanities, 1967 - 1986; F-50-3-2; 18 cm of textual records
    - Monthly Reports, 1975; F-50-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1976; F-50-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1977; F-50-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1978; F-50-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1979; F-50-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1980; F-50-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1981; F-50-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1981; F-50-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1982; F-50-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1983; F-50-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1984; F-50-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Monthly Reports, 1985; F-50-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Annual Reports, 1967 - 1976; F-50-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Reference Statistics, 1982 - 1985; F-50-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-50-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-23)
    - Social Sciences correspondence, vol. 1, 1968 - 1986; F-50-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/31.
    - Social Sciences correspondence, vol. 2, 1968 - 1986; F-50-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
    - Humanities Division, 1968 - 1977; F-50-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/61.
    - Amalgamation of Social Sciences and Humanities reference, 1981 - 1985; F-50-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-81)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/31/1.
  - Special projects and foundations, 1966 - 1980; F-50-3-3; 44 cm of textual records
    - Early Canadian Journals - Correspondence, 1967 - 1972; F-50-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Titles to be Considered, 1968; F-50-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Correspondence (Titles), 1969 - 1971; F-50-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Invoices, West Canadian Graphics, 1973 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Publicity, 1969 - 1970; F-50-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Progress Reports, 1969 - 1971; F-50-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Early Canadian Journals - Report on Donner Grant Project, 1971; F-50-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-24)
    - Institutional Correspondence - A (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1972 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - B (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1975; F-50-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - C (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1975; F-50-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - D (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1970 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - G (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - H (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - I (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1973 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - J (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971; F-50-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - L (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - M (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1970 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - N (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1976; F-50-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - O (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1972 - 1974; F-50-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-25)
    - Institutional Correspondence - P (Donnor Canadian Foundation), 1971 - 1975; F-50-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-25)